Guide to the Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archives ca. 1990-1997 MSS 86 MSS 086
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Publicity, photographs and sales catalogs
  - Subseries A: Publicity and promotion
    - Press binder--Vazquez Montalban, Manuel, Off Side, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Press binder--Vega, Ana Lydia, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - Press binder--Veronese, David, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - Press binder--Wakefield, Tom, Lot's Wife, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - Press binder--Wakefield, Tom, Ten Commandments, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 240)
    - Press binder--Wakefield, Tom, Variety Artistes, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - Press binder--Wakefield / Gale / King, Secret Lives, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 242)
    - Press binder--Walser, Robert, The Walk, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 243)
    - Press binder--Walser, Robert, Institute Benjamenta, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - Press binder--Weiss, Daniel Evan, Roaches Have No King, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - Press binder--Weiss, Daniel Evan, Swine's Wedding, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - Press binder--Weiss, Ernst, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Press binder--Weissman, Banjamin, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - Press binder--West, Paul, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Press binder--Wilkinson, Margaret, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - Press binder--Wilmer, Valerie, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - Press binder--Wittig Albert, Susan, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Press binder--Wodin, Natasha, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Press binder--Wright, Lawrence, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - Press binder--Wurlitzer, Rudolph, Quake, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 255)
    - Press binder--Wurlitzer, Rudolph, Nog, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Press binder--Wurlitzer, Rudolph, Flats, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Press kit, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Promotional materials--posters, stickers, press, sales kit (see flat box), undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 258a)
    - Sales kit for May 1993 sales conference, 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Sales kit--spring, 1994; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Sales kit--spring, 1994; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 261)
    - Sales kit--fall, 1994; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 262)
    - Sales kit--spring, 1995; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - Sales kit--fall, 1995; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - Sales kit--fall, 1995; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - Sales kit--fall, 1995; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Sales kit--spring / summer, 1996; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - Trade promotion, undated; 31142040617170 (Box 3, Folder 268)
  - Subseries B: Photographs
    - Photos--Acker, Kathy, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Photos--Ayrton, Pete, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Photos--Baratham, Gopal, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Photos--Bierman, Pieke, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Photos--Bornstein / Sullivan, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Photos--Burroughs, William, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Photos--Bush, Catherine, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Photos--Camus, Renaud, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Photos--Cooper, Fiona, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Photos--Cortez, Jayne, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Photos--County, Jayne, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Photos--Daeninckx, Didier, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Photos--Davis, Lydia, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Photos--Duffy, Stella, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Photos--Eltit, Diamela, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Photos--Fell, Alison, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Photos--Galas, Diamanda, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Photos--Gardiner, James, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Photos--Gilroy, Paul, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - Photos--Giorno, John, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - Photos--Glück, Robert, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - Photos--Gordon, Graeme, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - Photos--Grace, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Photos--Graham, Barry, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Photos--Greer, Bonnie, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Photos--Guibert, Herve., undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - Photos--Hall, Leah, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 295)
    - Photos--Hansbury, James, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 296)
    - Photos--Home, Stewart, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 297)
    - Photos--Indiana, Gary, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 298)
    - Photos--Jelinek, Elfriede, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 299)
    - Photos--Jordan, June, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - Photos--Kennedy, Pagan, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - Photos--Klein, Adam, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - Photos--Langford, Diane, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 303)
    - Photos--Lewis, Heather, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 304)
    - Photos--Maraini, Dacia, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 305)
    - Photos--Moyano, Daniel, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 306)
    - Photos--Meer, Ameena, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - Photos--Meyer, Stewart, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 308)
    - Photos--Montalban, Manuel Vasquez, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 309)
    - Photos--Nayman, Mich, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 310)
    - Photos--Olson, Jenni, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 311)
    - Photos--Onetti, Juan Carlos, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 312)
    - Photos--Pullinger, Kate, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - Photos--Raymond, Derek, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 314)
    - Photos--Rower, Ann, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    - Photos--Saer, Juan Jose, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 316)
    - Photos--Sanza, Sylvia, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 317)
    - Photos--Sapphire, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    - Photos--Scott, Mary, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    - Photos--Shaviro, Steven, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    - Photos--Silverberg, Ira and Amy Scholder, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - Photos--Smith, Jack, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    - Photos--Tillman, Lynne, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - Photos--Trinidad, David, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    - Photos--Valenzuela, Luisa, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 325)
    - Photos--Vega, Ana Lydia, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 326)
    - Photos--Veronese, David, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 327)
    - Photos--Weiss, Dan, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    - Photos--Weissman, Benjamin, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    - Photos--slides of cover art / authors, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 330)
  - Subseries C: Sales catalogues
    - Sales catalogues--Atlas Arkhive, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 331)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium, fall / winter, 1994; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 332)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (complete titles) spring / summer, 1995; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 333)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (new titles) spring / summer, 1995; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 334)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (new titles) fall / winter, 1995-1996; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 335)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (complete titles) fall / winter, 1995-1996; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 336)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium, spring / summer, 1996; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 337)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (complete reference catalogue), 1996; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 338)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (literature from Latin America & Spain from independent publishers), undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 339)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (poetry from independent publishers for course use), undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 340)
    - Sales catalogues--Consortium (world literature from independent publishers for classrooms & libraries), undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 341)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Apr. 1990-Mar. 1991, 1990-1991; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 342)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, fall 1990 / winter 1991, 1990-1991; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 343)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, spring / summer 1991, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 344)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Apr. 1991-Mar. 1992, 1991-1992; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 345)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, fall 1991 / winter 1992, 1991-1992; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 346)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Apr.-Dec. 1992, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 347)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, spring / summer 1992, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 348)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, autumn / winter 1992-93, 1992-1993; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 349)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Jan.-July 1993, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 350)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, spring / summer 1993, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 351)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Aug. 1993-Jan. 1994, 1993-1994; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 352)
    - Sales catalogues--ST/HR, fall / winter 1993-94, 1993-1994; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 353)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Feb.-Aug. 1994, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 354)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Apr.-Aug. 1994, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 355)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Sept. 1994-Feb. 1995, 1994-1995; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 356)
    - Sales catalogues--ST/HR, Nov. 1994-Mar. 1995, 1994-1995; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 357)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Mar.-Aug. 1995, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 358)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Sept. 1995-Feb. 1996, 1995-1996; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 359)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Mar.-Aug. 1996, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 360)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, fall 1996 (10th Anniversary, 1986-1996), 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 361)
    - Sales catalogues--ST 10th Anniversary special promotion, 1986-1996, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 362)
    - Sales catalogues--ST order forms, undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 363)
    - Sales catalogues--ST, Sept. 1996-Feb.1997, 1996-1997; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 364)
    - Sales catalogues--ST/HR (Midnight Classics, Mask Noir, Masks), undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 365)
    - Sales catalogues--ST/HR (Midnight Classics, Mask Noir, Atlas) fall 1995 / winter 1996, 1995-1996; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 366)
    - Sales catalogues--ST/HR (Midnight Classics, Mask Noir, Atlas) spring / summer 1996, 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 367)
    - Sales catalogues--ST/HR promotional booklets (excerpted material), undated; 31142040617188 (Box 4, Folder 368)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous
  - Subseries A: Subject files
    - Miller, Paul (a.k.a. DJ Spooky, The Subliminal Kid), undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Pieces written by Miller, Paul, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Paul (see flat box), undated (Box 1, Folder 2a)
    - Tremblay, Richard (a.k.a. Rick Trembles), undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Subseries B: Printed material
    - Eltit, Diamela, The Fourth World, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Green, Julien, L=Autre Sommeil, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Redstone calendar, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Redstone calendar, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Redstone calendar, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Subseries C: Ephemera
    - ST/HR banner; ST wristwatch, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Subseries D: Computer Disks
    General note
    [Items 10 & 11 are small gray boxes inside Box 1]
    - Computer disks, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Computer disks, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Accretion 2011 - Series VII: Cookie Mueller Material
  - "The Anti-Memoirs of Cookie Mueller" in City Paper, Baltimore, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Artwork and Sketches, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cookie Mueller- Cover Letter and Resume, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cookie Mueller- Personal Documents, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Details Magazine Clippings, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Drugs" Screenplay, Manuscript, and Notes, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings and Drafts (mixed), 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - High Times with "Ask Cookie Mueller" section, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - MAD Magazine, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mailing list, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Pages [1 of 2], 1970-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript pages [2 of 2], 1970-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Manuscripts [1 of 2], undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Manuscripts [2 of 2], Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Manuscripts- Published or Duplicates, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mixed Loose Materials, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Notebooks, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Notes and Fragments, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Photocopied articles [1 of 2], 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Photocopied articles [2 of 2], 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Science News Magazine, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Screenplay Manuscripts, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Semiotext(e) Book- Stories and Chapters, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Stories and Drafts, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Story ideas / synopses, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "The Anti-Memoirs of Cookie Mueller" [flat box], undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - "Brenda Losing" by Cookie Mueller [flat box], undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cookie Mueller wedding photographs [flat box], undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Empire State Building / King Kong paper cut-out template [flat box], undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "San Francisco 1967" by Cookie Mueller, in Vacation magazine [flat box], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Flat box-Series I: Author Files
  - Subseries A: High Risk author files
    - Galas, Diamanda--misc, undated (Box 1, Folder 55a)
    - Rower, Ann--poster, undated (Folder 194a)
- Flat box-Series V:: Publicity, photographs and sales catalogs
  - Subseries A: Publicity and promotion
    - Cover flats, undated (Folder 8a)
    - ST/HR promotional material (posters, stickers, press, sales kit), undated (Folder 258a)
- Flat box-Series VI: Miscellaneous
  - Subseries A: Subject Files
    - Miller, Paul (a.k.a. DJ Spooky, The Subliminal Kid), undated (Folder 2a)
    - Margot Mifflin, AA Literary Miner, New York Times 13 Mar. 1994, late ed.: Sec. 9 (Folder 1)
    - Ibid, undated (Folder 2)
    - Ibid, undated (Folder 3)